(Sheldon:)Uh-huh. And if I don't want to forfeit
the award?
(Sheldon:)Well, you've got that tied up
in a neat little bow.
(Sheldon:)All right, thank you.
(Sheldon:)-Problem.
-What?
(Sheldon:)They expect me to give a speech
at the banquet.
(Sheldon:)I can't give a speech.
(Howard:)Well, no, you're mistaken.
You give speeches all the time.
(Howard:)What you can't do is shut up.
(Raj:)Yeah, before the movie,
you did 20 minutes...
(Raj:)...on why guacamole turns brown.
(Raj:)Turned brown
while you were talking.
I'm perfectly comfortable speaking
to small groups.
(Sheldon:)I cannot speak to large crowds.
(Leonard:)What to you is a large crowd?
(Sheldon:)Any group big enough
to trample me to death.
(Sheldon:)General rule of thumb is 36 adults
or 70 children.
(Penny:)Sheldon. Congratulations.
(Penny:)Brought you cheesecake from work.
You know, because of your award,
not because that busboy sneezed on it.